





Summary

Jump to Section

Achievement-driven professional with an experience of nearly 6 years in development of web applications using Mcrosoft

Comprehensive experience in designing systems/ procedures for change in project operations to design technical solutions, ensuring business functionality adherence and enhancing competitive advantage

Hands-on experience in Analysis, Implementation, Testing & Development Of Business Applications using 3-Tier & N-Tier Architecture with C#.Net, VB.NET ASP.NET, ADO.NET, M/C, Web Services, WPF, Web API, JavaScript, JQuery, Mcrosoft Azure, AngularJS

Knowledge in:

- Coding DB Procedures and Functions & Triggers
- Mcrosoft Visual Source Safe (VSS), Team Foundation Server (TFS) SVN and Visual Studio

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

Insightful knowledge of business process analysis and design, application based process optimization, cost control and revenue maximization from various solutions

Work Experience

Virtusa Consulting Services Pvt. Ltd as IT Consultant

Sep 2019 to Till Date

Qatar Airways; Frequent Flyer Program, Qatarairways.Com, Sales Platform (Business Critical Projects) (Onsite Project, Qatar)

Technologies Used: WPF, MVC, WebApi, WCF and AJAX

Role: Developer

Description:

Qatarairways. Com site is key that holds major revenue generator for Qatar Airways. Redemption & Cash Plus Miles plays a key role in attracting passengers to fly on Qatar Airways which happens to be the key revenue generator for Qatar Airways. QLAS is the back-end application for contact service agents which can be utilised to complete the bookings offline and as well as all the key information related to Frequent Flyer Program which the PAX accumulates for the journeys and ticket bookings

Karvy Computershare Pvt. Ltd. as Software Engineer Jan 2017 to Sep 2019

Team Strength: 10 Members

Technologies: ASP.NET, VB.NET, SQL Server, WCF, AJAX, JQuery, 3-Tier Architecture, and ITEXT Sharp

Role: Developer

Description:

Kbolt is Karvy Business Online Transactions Application. This application is designed for the entry of Mutual Fund application forms which come to branches directly. There are different types of modules: entry modules (purchase, redemption and switch) and retrieving modules (Query, reports); this application is used for maintaining for 21 funds like (RMF, Axis, UTI)

Important

· Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld

Responsibilities:

Administered production issues and steered the enhancement of existing live portals
Contributed in Database Design; developed database tables, stored procedures using SQL Server
Formed relationships between database tables as per business logic of the application
Created Application in N tier architecture

Priya Sharma Software Pvt. Ltd as Software Engineer Jun 2014 to Jul 2016

^ Back to Top

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E (Bectrical) from auroras scientific and technological institute in 2008

^ Back to Top

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
C#, VB.NET			
ASP.NET M/C, HTML, Ajax			
JavaScript, JQuery			
MS Word, Excel, PowerPoint			
MongoDB, SQL Server 2008			
Bit Bucket (Tortoise Hg)			
3-Layer Architecture,N-Tier Architecture			
Microsoft Visual Source Safe			
Visual Studio 2010/2013/2015			
MS .Net Framework 3.0/ 3.5/ 4.0			
Entity Framework LINQ to SQL			
MVC, C#, JQuery, MongoDB			

^ Back to Top

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Physically Challenged: No

Category: General

Job Type: Permanent
Employment Status: Full time

Work Authorization

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQs - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.